goprocessing.in 2013-09-15

# Leading Aggregator for Recharge and Payment Solutions | GoProcessing.in

##### This privacy policy sets out how **GO PROCESSING INDIA PRIVATE LIMITED**

(CIN: U93000DL2011PTC220967) 

**Registered office:**  
A-275, 2nd Floor, Okhla Industrial Area  
Phase 1, New Delhi - 110020 

Incorporated under the Companies Act, 1956 ( No.1 of 1956 ) and that the company is private limited. Uses and protects any information that You give Us when You use this website.

We are committed to ensuring that Your privacy is protected. Should We ask You to provide certain information by which You can be identified when using this website, then You can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that You are happy with any changes.

#### What Go Processing collects

Go Processing may collect the following information:  

  * Name and job title.
  * Contact information including email address.
  * Credit or debit card information.
  * Mobile telephone number and network details.
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.

####  What Go Processing does with the information

Go Processing gathers they require this information to understand Your needs and provide You with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:  

  * Your information will enable Go Processing to provide you with the access to all parts of Go Processing website and to supply the goods or services you have requested.
  * Your information will also enable Go Processing to bill you and to contact you where necessary concerning your orders and your ongoing account with Go Processing.
  * Go Processing may use the information to administer, improve and develop products and services.
  * In particular, Go Processing may use the information to contact you for your views on services and to notify you occasionally about important changes or developments to the website or services.
  * Go Processing may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, Go Processing may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. Go Processing may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. Go Processing may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
  * Internal record keeping.

#### Security

Go Processing is committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, Go Processing have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information that collect online. Go Processing will retain your information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires.

#### Links to other websites

Go Processing website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave Go Processing site, You should note that Go Processing does not have any control over that other website. Therefore, Go Processing cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

#### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways :  

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes.
  * If you have previously agreed to Go Processing using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing Go Processing.

Go Processing will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless Go Processing have your permission or are required by law to do so. Go Processing may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which Go Processing thinks you may find interesting if you tell Go Processing that you wish this to happen.

#### Accessing and updating

You are entitled to see the information held about you and you may ask Go Processing to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. You may request details of personal information which Go Processing holds about you under the Data Protection Act. A small fee will be payable.

#### Contact

All comments, queries and requests relating to Go Processing uses of your information are welcomed and should be addressed to :

**Go Processing India Private Limited**  
A275, 2nd Floor, Okhla Industrial Area  
Phase-1, New Delhi - 110020  
**Phone:** +91 11 6666 2323  
**Fax:** +1 111 123-45-67  
**Email:**[info@goprocessing.in](mailto:info@goprocessing.in)
